Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
What the hell are you doing?
We're waiting on the concrete.
You're holding everyone up.
I haven't stopped all day.
Can't I take a break for 2 minutes?
You're too slow.
You need to speed up.
I will. but my hands hurt.
Where are your gloves?
You need to wear them.
I always have mine on.
It's too hard with the shovel.
I said I'd do it.
Who wants some. guys?
Who is she?
Your girlfriend?
Not yet.
But I'm working on it.
Seriously. guys.
It's private.
She's a knockout. Look.
Yeah. she's cute.
You know her name?
Not yet.
She's pretty anyhow.
- I'm not interested in that.
- I am.
Hold on.
You're sure that's her?
No. but it's a real photo.
Don't show him! He's a kid.
Please. he's seen worse.
You can't even see her face.
Still. she's not bad.
It's hard to say.
She's fit. though.
Hear him!
He must get all the girls.
It's not like that.
You don't get laid a lot?
Average. I guess.
What does that mean?
It means average.
If he's not getting laid at 16.
he won't ever.
I see the windows are in.
Only the first set.
- What about the second?
- By Friday.
That doesn't look straight.
Don't worry. he's getting better.
But we'll go over it.
I'll walk you out.
This is rubbish work!
You made me look stupid.
On top of all the defects.
it's not even plumb.
You've never used a bob?
Dammit. we won't make the deadline.
And you.
I told you to supervise!
- What were you doing?
- My work.
He wastes all my time.
I did all this.
You can't redo everything!
You have to watch him.
or he'll fuck up.
Where's he going now?
Where are you going?
This is bullshit.
Get in the car. I'm taking you home.
- And my bike?
- Get it tomorrow.
What's your parents' address?
I've always taken on apprentices.
Always.
But you're the sloppiest by far.
You know what pisses me off?
You don't care. At all.
You're always late.
you never listen to anything...
That's not true.
I've only been late three times.
You'll never get your certificate.
It's been eight months.
And you still can't stack
two breeze blocks properly.
I should let you go.
Loads of kids deserve the job more.
What?
You need to turn right here.
It's the gate over there.
Is anyone home?
- Should I take off my shoes?
- No.
Guests can keep them on.
It's my boss. Mr. Corelli.
He wants to talk to you.
Offer him something to drink.
We're coming.
Would you like a drink?
A glass of water.
Not a beer?
No. water's fine. Thanks.
Thank you.
Hello.
We've spoken on the phone
but never met.
Yes. of course.
Excuse us. we'd gone for a dip.
It's no problem at all.
I won't keep you long.
Have a seat.
So...
What's going on?
Is there a problem
Nothing serious.
I wanted to talk about Enzo.
It's not serious.
but maybe Enzo isn't quite suited
to a building site.
He's an intelligent kid.
just not very great with his hands.
And not motivated enough.
Wait.
are you're saying
you won't keep him on?
Not at all.
I'm saying it for his sake.
It'd be good for him
to think about
what he really wants to do.
Maybe something other than masonry.
At the training college.
his teachers agree.
To be honest.
when Enzo chose this path.
it surprised us.
It's because he was struggling
with the school system.
But it's still your choice.
isn't it?
Yes.
So what do you say?
I'm fine with it.
What does that mean?
What does?
Bricklaying.
Mr. Corelli doesn't seem to agree.
It's just I messed up a bit today.
I still like the job.
Apparently.
the problem's ongoing.
I'll make an effort.
I enjoy what I'm doing.
I'm learning a lot.
I'm happy to hear that.
We're here to train you.
But we won't get anywhere
if you don't try.
No worries.
I'll try to concentrate more.
So I can count on you?
Yeah.
Well. I'll be off then.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Thanks for taking the time.
So I'll see you tomorrow?
Yeah. tomorrow...
All right?
So... How are you feeling?
The pressure's mounting?
We're already sick of revisions.
How are you?
This is pretty.
- I've my swimsuit on too.
- Good idea.
- I'll make some coffee.
- Thanks.
It's good Mr. Corelli came by.
He seems nice.
He's nice to you.
but actually he's an arsehole.
Stop it.
I found him perceptive.
Enzo?
Yes?
Everything okay?
Yeah. fine. Why?
Don't stay three hours
in the shower.
Your brother's really built.
Totally.
- He's grown.
- Shut up!
No one touches my brother.
I don't need your permission.
He is underage. though.
Yeah. I'll call the cops.
Right. guys. I'm going in!
We've worked enough.
You didn't come here
to study at all...
- You're not swimming?
- No. I can't be bothered.
Show me your hands.
Not getting better?
It's ok.
but the chlorine doesn't help.
Let's sort them out. Come on.
I don't understand.
you're not stupid.
I'm sure if you went back to school.
you'd easily catch up.
Can you listen to me
for two minutes?
I am. but I know
what you're going to say.
No. you don't.
Marion. please...
Sorry. I'm just checking an email.
Dinner looks good today.
There's a private school in Marseille
that would really suit you.
It's a facility that takes drop-outs.
for kids like you. not suited
to the traditional system.
I don't like
that expression "drop-out".
How would you say it?
I'm just sick
of these stupid expressions.
I'm not a drop-out.
I was just bad at school.
You weren't bad.
'Bad' means nothing.
You just didn't make an effort.
I didn't understand anything.
Let's just say
you don't always try.
You are a bit thick.
So. at this school.
you'd thrive
with their teaching methods.
Forget about the baccalaureate.
I care about your development.
Why do you keep insisting?
You won't convince him like that.
I have a student I like.
The other day. we spoke about you.
He told me. at your age.
he was failing school.
and that his teachers
didn't believe in his future.
Well. something clicked.
Now he's a great PhD candidate.
That's your dream?
No. not that you do maths.
I just want you to have
bigger ambitions. That's all.
Well you see.
my ambitions are very small.
That's not true.
You loved your art lessons.
And you're talented.
Yeah. you drew really well.
Don't you start too.
Look...
It's awesome.
It's true.
that sketch is beautiful.
Of course it is.
Seriously. stop it.
I don't like it hung on display.
like a trophy.
Because it's a deer?
It does look a bit
like a hunting trophy.
True.
You could try for the Beaux-Arts.
Or another art school.
- I'm not an artist.
- You've no idea.
What are you afraid of?
The thing is.
I don't want to study anymore.
I want to work.
I like what I'm doing.
working with my hands.
Something that lasts...
Those are just words.
Fine. but look at this house...
Imagine a tsunami. a disaster. anything.
Everyone dies.
All that's left will be
walls and buildings.
Something man-made.
No bodies. nothing.
Just walls.
And that's why I like what I do.
Well. that's a cheerful thought...
Stop being a smartarse.
You need to understand something.
I won't go back to school.
So you'll be a bricklayer
your whole life.
So what?
Is that shameful?
You studied 10 years for what?
A professor who spouts lessons
to bored minds behind desks
in a closed room.
Enzo.
you're being unpleasant.
Screw this.
Where are you going?
Come back.
Do you have any ideas
for the summer?
You'll come away with us
for a few days?
I don't think it's the right time
to raise with Corelli.
You're allowed a vacation.
I want to book soon.
I was thinking Italy.
The beautiful house near Naples.
Remember?
Sure. why not...
Such enthusiasm...
You liked it though?
Yeah. it was cool.
You have to be sure.
It'll cost an arm and leg to cancel.
I hate that expression.
You do?
As if I'd blow you up.
It's just an expression.
What's wrong?
How much do you earn?
Why do you ask?
I dunno.
we've never talked about it.
Of course not.
We don't want to bore you
with money stuff.
Tell me. don't be ashamed.
I'm not ashamed.
Honestly...
I earn an engineer's salary.
Which means?
Around 6.000 euros a month.
You know the exact amount?
No. because sometimes...
I get bonuses
on top of that.
And Dad?
A little less.
But close.
Remember to ask Corelli
about holidays.
Yeah.
You're on fire today.
You're the ones doing nothing.
You okay?
Yeah.
Why were you arguing with Vlad?
It's nothing. don't worry.
You know. Vlad's complicated.
We'll have to go back to Ukraine.
Really?
We've received papers.
To go fight.
In the war?
Yes. in the war.
We're 25 now.
They can't force you
can they?
They won't come and get us.
but it's our duty.
We have to
or it won't be our country anymore.
And Vlad doesn't want to?
Vlad says he's French
and that he wants to stay.
I know he's pretending.
He's not happy here.
He's an idiot.
What did Mummy make you today?
Are you going to ask me
every day?
Shut up and eat your shitty pâté.
So I hear you live
in a billionaire's villa.
That's bullshit.
Corelli said it's huge.
with a big pool and everything.
News travels fast.
You hid that from us.
I didn't hide anything.
You never asked me.
Where do you live?
You Know the coastal road?
Where the beautiful villas are.
The nicest neighbourhood.
With a sea view...
I'd like to see your house.
When'll you invite us?
It's not my place.
What do you mean?
- It's my parents'.
- It's the same thing.
I'd like to meet them too.
Especially your mum!
She'd barely look at you.
We'll see about that.
All right?
Yes. always.
Ah. great.
You're finally wearing your gloves.
Your hands are important.
You got to protect them.
Look...
I cut off my finger once.
Really?
Yeah. look...
See...
Here's the tip.
Wow...
But it grew back.
That was my hand.
That must've hurt.
Yeah. like a bitch.
After that. you're screwed.
So you have a big house?
With a pool...
Yeah...
What the fuck
are you doing here then?
I don't get it.
What?
If my parents had money.
I'd go into business.
open a restaurant...
or do nothing at all.
Nothing's good.
Your parents are in Ukraine?
In Kyiv.
You've heard from them?
Yeah. they're okay.
Have they been bombed?
No.
But my brother's fighting.
And I have friends who died.
Wow. that's rough.
Yeah. rough...
What about you?
Do you plan to go back?
No. I don't want to.
Really?
Why would I go back?
To fight. for your family.
I don't want to.
Are you scared?
No. I'm not scared.
But I don't want to die
because of that bastard Putin.
Aren't you worried
you'll be accused of deserting?
What?
Deserting?
Deserting's when you won't fight
for your country.
I know. but that's not me.
I'm not old enough.
Miroslav said you were called up.
Miroslav was. but not me.
He said he'd go.
but he's still here.
He makes me laugh.
I didn't mean to offend...
Just watch your fucking mouth!
I'm not a kid.
Come on. move it!
Guys. what's up?
Why the bad mood?
I'm fine.
He's the moody one.
He acts tough. but he's cool.
Tonight. we're going out
for drinks and a pizza.
After. we'll hit up a club.
You wanna come?
Are you sure?
Of course.
Look. Vlad's already over it.
Can I go home to shower first?
Come to our place and shower.
and then we'll head out.
If you don't want to. tell me.
It's up to you.
Look. he's happy now!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Your favourite pizza?
Any. I like them all.
After you. my lord.
I joined the army at 14.
I was a kadetzki.
a cadet.
See. this is me.
With a very good friend.
Did you go into combat?
No. I was too young.
And then...
I left when I turned 18.
For the Foreign Legion.
Here's my white kepi.
Where was that?
In Mali. in Africa.
See this? It was a sandstorm.
This was also in Mali.
We did patrols
with armoured cars.
It was tough.
The drones and all the guns scared me.
It was very difficult.
This photo is me and my mum.
After Africa.
they gave me three weeks' leave.
So I went home to see my mum.
I stayed in Ukraine the whole time.
A great memory.
What's he said about me?
Nothing...
Don't listen to him. It's all bullshit.
He hates being talked about.
Why?
I don't know.
Was he in the army too?
Not at all.
but he doesn't get on with his parents.
So he moved to Belgium. Germany...
He's never settled down.
There's no vibe here.
What are you doing?
In Ukraine. we say nasdrovia.
Strong stuff!
Come on. dance.
Come on.
You can do it.
What are clubs for? Dancing.
You're getting it.
Don't worry.
Look. it's not real.
In the Foreign Legion.
I was in charge of weaponry.
I'm ready for the Russians.
Don't listen to him.
Go and shower...
Here. try this on.
Got anything simpler?
Like a t-shirt?
I'm not used to wearing shirts.
No. you have to dress up for the club.
Is it a club for losers?
You're all talk.
Try it on. you'll see.
See. you look good.
But the shirt
needs to be open.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
You'll be sexier.
Look. you're handsome like that.
Women will go for you.
Lisa!
This is Enzo.
He works with us at the site.
Hi. Enzo.
What did she say?
Don't worry. Nothing bad.
She's joking.
In you go.
How old are you?
19...
19?
Got your ID?
No. not on me.
Go home and get it.
Come on...
Let him in. please.
No ID. he doesn't get in.
It's fine.
You sure?
Yeah. no worries.
What are you doing up?
I was worried.
what do you think.
I never asked you
to wait up for me.
I tried to call you all night.
I had no battery.
Right.
How convenient.
Why would I lie?
But where were you?
I was in a place
where there's life and people.
What does that mean?
If you must know...
I went to a club
with guys from the site.
A club?
You know. where people go to dance.
They let you in?
Yeah. why not?
Because you're 16.
Who were you with?
Who are these colleagues?
Vlad and Miroslav.
They're Ukrainian.
They're really cool.
What are those clothes?
They lent them to me.
They're not you.
Maybe not...
But still...
It was the best night of my life.
You should be happy for me.
Wait...
Enzo's changed so much in a year.
He was so scrawny as a kid.
He spends all his time exercising.
So what?
It's a good thing at his age.
He works hard too.
His job's strenuous.
It's normal he's changing.
How is he doing?
Is he holding up?
Actually. I think so.
He's not complaining.
If he complained.
he'd be admitting
the job doesn't suit him.
What can you do?
We can't make him do what we want.
he's too old for that.
It's no time to give up.
Maybe it's just a phase.
He's still young.
Nothing's final at that age.
Look at Leïla.
she had a bad patch two years ago.
She was smoking non-stop.
she was unpleasant.
missed half her classes...
It's true.
Then. all of a sudden.
in the space of three months.
she changed completely.
Somehow. she became independent.
self-assured...
with lots of plans.
You worry about your kids.
you want them to fall in line.
and when they do.
you miss their wildness a bit.
I don't want Enzo to conform.
I never said that.
But you'd like him to be like you.
Not at all.
In any case.
when you see him like that.
he seems fine.
Maybe he actually likes the job.
Please. that's too easy.
With your kids doing architecture
or at a top school. you're fine.
You don't see your son
leave for a construction site
and come back home a wreck.
He's 16.
He's a 16-year-old kid hurting himself.
It's shit.
It's like he's drowning
right in front of us.
and we're letting him.
Here. 13 metres.
Here. we have...
10.
10 metres on this side...
7.50 metres here.
Now work out the surface area.
How's it going?
Good. and you?
So. what are we doing?
We could go to my place for once.
Would you like that?
Will we be alone?
Yeah. my parents are at work.
And your brother?
He's revising a lot with his mates.
Shall we go then?
All right.
My feelings don't change. it's a threat
I gotta love but hate intercepts
Lord. where we going?
Don't know yet
Smoke in the air. regrets I forget
Something feels off. I'm a wreck
Ain't in the mood for a fest
Dunno what it is. got pain in my head
Too few understand. Mama
Too much I bled. Mama
You draw really well.
I dunno. but I like to.
You draw better than you rap.
Come on. I thought you'd like it.
Is she a girl you slept with?
Of course not.
You can see it's a statue.
I know. I'm kidding.
Do you think you could draw me?
I prefer statues.
Seriously?
I mean
for drawing.
I hate the idea of making someone
keep still for hours.
I'm willing to do it for you.
You're really beautiful.
Want to have a swim?
Now?
Why not?
I didn't bring my swimsuit.
That's okay.
Swim in your underwear.
We're alone.
Okay. if you swim in your boxers.
Hold on.
What?
It's just for me. don't worry.
Hold on. your hair's a mess.
Thanks.
Your mum's here!
Yeah?
You said no one was here.
She's home early.
So embarrassing.
Amina. a friend... My mum.
Hello. Amina.
Hello. madam.
Act like I'm not here.
I'll just put the shopping away.
Invite Amina to dinner if you want.
Thanks. but I can't stay.
As you want.
Another time maybe?
Maybe. Thank you.
What's your mum after?
She just offered...
It's weird though.
Why?
If my parents found us naked.
they wouldn't invite you to dinner!
Mine don't care.
My brother even has girlfriends
over for the night.
- I have to go.
- Wait. I'll give you a ride.
I feel like walking.
Damn. you're annoying!
Why did you turn up like that?
I couldn't know you weren't alone.
Can't I have a minute of privacy?
Come on. you weren't exactly
having sex by the pool...
Shut up!
I'll help you.
Want to do a job with me
this weekend?
The pay is 150 euros.
Just the two of us.
Miroslav doesn't want it?
He won't be here.
He never is at weekends.
He's at his girl's.
Interested or not?
You bet.
Have you got a girlfriend too?
Yes. of course.
Stop lying.
I don't believe you.
It's true.
Then show me.
You've got a photo?
- Don't hide her.
- Let me find one.
- Wait a second.
- I'll choose one myself.
Hold on.
I've found one.
You're beautiful together.
You think so?
Yeah.
That's real love.
I dunno...
And do you have any photos?
Yes. of course.
Even videos. but they're too hot.
I showed you. you can show me.
Your mum wouldn't like me
showing you porn.
I won't tell her.
Here.
- The girl from the other night?
- Yes.
Not bad. huh?
She's your girlfriend?
No.
He can't do anything without me.
Oh. you're here.
Can you help us out?
I won't be able to come.
Are you serious?
I have a job tomorrow.
What do you mean?
A cash job...
A colleague offered to me.
No. this needs to stop.
No. it's 150 euros for two days.
Are you kidding?
You wanted to go diving.
I booked everything.
I accepted already.
I can't let him down now.
Go without me. it's no big deal.
What do you mean. no big deal?
Can't you manage without me?
We don't have to be stuck together
all the time.
You know what?
I'll cancel the boat.
- But I want to dive.
- I don't anymore.
I work too. you know.
I wanted to relax a bit.
Drop it. Victor. okay.
So I have to lose out
just because you're pissed off?
Watch your tone!
Everything's ready! This sucks.
Shit. it's crazy.
The more he screws up
they more you let him.
I'm sick of causing shit.
Shut the fuck up. you!
I don't like the way
you're looking at us.
What?
Do you think I
don't have two eyes?
You despise us!
Yes?
It's me. Enzo.
Enzo?
Come on in.
Come in.
What's up?
I have problems with my parents.
Do you think I could
sleep here tonight?
As Miroslav isn't here.
Sure. you can take his bed
if you want.
That way. we can go to the job
together tomorrow.
I don't know if his bed is clean.
You want to change the sheets?
No. I'm not bothered.
So. what happened with your parents?
I had a fight. with my dad mainly...
Over bullshit stuff.
I understand. It happens.
One day. I was so mad at my dad.
I hit him.
You did?
You're not answering?
He won't stop calling if you don't.
I don't care.
Maybe he's worried.
I've nothing to say to him.
Hello?
Hello. where are you?
This isn't Enzo.
Who is it?
A colleague. a friend of Enzo's.
Put my son on.
Put him on. please.
- He can't talk now.
- Put him on!
He isn't here. he's taking a shower.
He's fine.
you don't need to worry.
I nearly called the police.
No. don't do that.
Your son's a good kid.
He won't do anything stupid.
I don't know. he's complicated...
You have to trust him.
Okay. thanks.
but ask him to call me back. please.
I'll try.
Goodbye.
Your father called.
You spoke to him?
I told him you were fine.
You're lucky to have a father
who worries about you.
You say that. but you hit yours.
I hit him because he always hit me.
You understand?
That's why you left Ukraine?
No.
Because of the war then?
No. I left to make money.
It must be difficult though.
being here and knowing
your friends and family
are in danger.
When I see the reports.
I feel I should go there.
Some French guys have.
What the hell would you do there?
Keep on watching TV. it's wiser.
If you decided to go back to Ukraine.
I'd definitely go with you.
What are you talking about?
I wouldn't be afraid with you.
You think I can
protect you from bombs?
No. of course not. but...
I wouldn't be afraid.
You're not afraid of dying?
Not with you.
Let's stop there. okay?
Damn. what time is it?
Time to go.
Why didn't you wake me?
You were sleeping like a baby.
You really needed it.
Tonight. it's best you go back home
to your parents.
Why?
Your parents will worry.
I'll call them.
No. go home.
Just let me stay tonight. please.
Get in. I'll take you home.
Aren't you getting out?
What are you waiting for?
Stop.
I don't want to. okay?
I just want to stay with you.
What are you hoping for?
That you'll suck me off?
And then what?
Then what?
It's better if
you don't come tomorrow.
I'll finish the pool on my own.
Okay. sweetheart?
Shit...
Are you stressed?
It seems they'll only take
two non-Parisians this year.
What's up?
They're only taking two non-Parisians.
Who told you that?
We saw it on Twitter.
I'm so sick of all this crap...
Go through the hole
and follow the tube.
Then go over that one.
straight to the junction box.
You're giving me
the silent treatment today?
No. why?
You haven't spoken to me all day.
Here. this is for you.
Keep your money.
You earned it.
It's your money.
Don't touch me!
I thought you liked it.
Bastard!
I'm just kidding.
Stop.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Stop.
Calm down.
Are you okay?
Get off me!
- For the oven?
- Yes. it's just there.
There you are!
We were starting to worry.
- What's going on?
- Victor got into Henri IV.
That's great.
All his friends got good places too.
You aren't going
to congratulate him?
Of course.
I'll miss you.
You're a beast. bro.
Careful. my shoulder hurts.
This'll do you good.
Go easy. you're not used to it.
It's fine. let him celebrate.
You've found a place in Paris?
Mum's friend has an Airbnb
we can rent for a year
Where is it?
- In the 11th.
- Nice.
Loads of bars and restaurants...
What are you doing in the dark?
Just checking on you.
You're being weird. I'm fine.
What is that bruise?
It's nothing. I hit myself at work.
Maybe you need an X-ray.
It's nothing. I told you.
Come back up.
We're waiting for you.
Stop it.
What's wrong with you?
Let her go!
No! Stop!
Calm down. it's a fake.
Fucking psycho!
You always have to ruin everything!
Fucking maniac!
Get out.
Now. tell me what's wrong.
I'm just having fun.
No. cut it out.
You're not ok. I can see that.
You'd like that. but I'm not.
I asked you something.
What's your problem?
I don't know.
I don't want this life.
All this stuff. all these people.
partying as if everything's fine.
I'm just not like you.
Not like us how?
As if you can't tell.
I don't belong in this house.
You know what?
You're just a spoiled kid
telling himself stories.
You're not strong.
you're shaking like a leaf.
- You're scared to death.
- So?
Being scared is normal.
Aren't you scared?
I'm scared for you!
Because you're hurting yourself.
That bruise on your back.
how did you get it?
Paolo. what's going on?
- I do what I want.
- No!
We're still responsible for you.
If you're hurt at work. we need to know.
You had an accident?
No. no accident.
I was in a fight.
- In a fight?
- Who with?
You don't know him.
The guy whose place you slept at?
His name's Vlad.
Why? Did you argue?
What did he do to you?
Tell me. or I'll ask him myself.
He's my boyfriend.
He fucks me. And I love him.
That's how it is.
What are you saying?
He fucks you?
He fucks you...
But...
You're a minor.
I do as I want.
You maybe. but not him.
His name's Vlad. you said?
- This isn't right.
- Calm down.
- That's enough!
- It's rape.
Why should I calm down?
No. it's not like that.
This guy can't do that to you. okay?
Calm down.
Tell me exactly what happened.
Did you sleep together?
Look at me.
Why make this stuff up?
Leave us alone for a bit.
See to the guests. I'll stay with him.
I don't know why I said that.
So nothing happened between you?
No.
That's why you're sad?
I don't want to talk about it.
Everything okay?
Yes.
He just drank a bit too much.
He needs to sleep.
Come here. guys. Gather round. please!
Please!
Fraz and Hamza.
finish up here the next two weeks.
Sébastien and Amada.
after the coating. I have a new job.
Three partitions to demolish...
The others
can clean up the exterior. okay?
Actually.
there's a problem.
Vlad and I won't be here for the end.
Why not? Off on holiday?
Thanks for telling me.
We're going back to Ukraine.
Really?
When are you leaving?
In two weeks.
That's a hassle. but...
I'll find a solution.
Okay. back to work.
What are you doing?
Send the rolls down
and then we're done.
What happened?
I don't know. I didn't see.
How do you feel?
My head hurts.
What do we do?
We can't leave him like this.
He needs a hospital.
I'll call an ambulance.
Give him some air.
Don't move.
Just keep still.
How do you feel?
You gave us a scare.
The scan showed nothing.
I know. they told us.
It's just a fractured wrist.
You need to keep still for your back.
It was quite a fall.
It could've been much worse.
You'll be obliged to rest now.
That's not so bad.
We'll take good care of you.
don't worry.
He's awake.
- You could have called me.
- He just woke up.
Don't stay in the dark.
It's a lovely day.
So.
you're not in too much pain?
I ache all over. but it's okay.
You'll need a physiotherapist
or an osteopath
to check things over time.
We'll see about that later.
Right. sweetheart?
Hello?
Hey. Enzo.
Can you hear me?
Yes. I hear you.
Where are you?
I'm in Italy.
And is Italy beautiful?
Yes. very beautiful.
Am I disturbing you?
No. not at all.
I didn't expect your call.
I'm with my parents. visiting ruins.
There are lots of ruins here too.
Where are you?
Near Kherson.
I dunno where that is.
It's in Eastern Ukraine.
And you're okay?
Yes. I'm okay.
There's a French guy here.
so we talk about France.
He's from Avignon.
Shame. he's a bit of a jerk.
Yeah. shame.
Are you well?
Yes. I'm okay.
You're going back to the site?
No. I don't think so.
What'll you do then?
I'm going to New York for a year.
Yeah? Nice...
I need to learn English.
It'll be a change from construction.
My parents arranged it.
There's no need to justify yourself.
Hello?
You heard that?
It landed close by.
No. I didn't hear it.
That one I heard.
I can't take it anymore.
It's like that all day long.
Shit.
Are you afraid?
What do you think?
Of course I'm afraid.
Sorry. I'm an idiot.
Don't worry. no offence.
So? Were you in love with me?
Yes. I think so.
You think so?
Yes.
Does that bother you?
No. it makes me happy.
Will you come back?
I hope so.
I really hope so.
Are you there?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today